Mexico
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Mexico, 2.1.1.1.15
  - Rurales, native police, 1911; 15; 13205; M212; 4x5 (Box 1202)
  - Native huts, 1911; 16; 13214; M266; 4x5 film (Box 1202)
  - Burro in doorway, 1911; 17; 13214; M305; 4x5 film (Box 1202)
  - Trolley car, 1911; 18; 13214; M331; 4x5 film (Box 1202)
  - Bull fight, 1911; 19; 13216; M218; 4x5 film (Box 1202)
  - Dead horse in ring, 1911; 20; 13216; M220; 4x5 film (Box 1202)
  - Bull fight, 1911; 21; 13216; M222; 4x5 film (Box 1202)
  - Bull fight, 1911; 22; 13216; M231; 4x5 film (Box 1202)
  - Bull fight, 1911; 23; 13216; M233; 4x5 film (Box 1202)
  - Bull fight, 1911; 24; 13216; M237; 4x5 film (Box 1202)